Artifacts Register, 1879-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
- Preludes Banner/1996, 301; cotton sheet
  Reads "Preludes: To boldly go where no man has gone before". With handprints.
- Preludes Banner/1994, 302; cotton sheet
  Reads "Preludes 1994: Once in a lifetime". With handprints and signatures.
- Mary Augusta Jordan Medal/N.D., 303; 2" across bronze
  Described under #14. See accompanying documentation.
  AASC.
- Phi Beta Kappa Pin/1910, 304; 0.5" x 1" gold
  Standard Phi Beta Kappa key.
  Belonged to Katherine Stevens 1910. AASC via Helen W. Simonds, friend of Stevens.
  97A-
- Phi Beta Kappa Pendant/1945, 305; 0.5" x 1" gold
  Standard Phi Beta Kappa key. On gold chain.
  Belonged to Helen Stobbe 1945.
  98A-29
- Phi Beta Kappa Pendant/1919, 306; 0.5" x 1" gold
  Standard Phi Beta Kappa key. Came on black velvet ribbon which was discarded.
  Belonged to Margaret Culberson 1919.
- Phi Beta Kappa Pendant/1909, 307; 0.5" x 1" gold
  Belonged to Mary L. Ellis 1909.
- Class of 1883 Parasol/N.D., 308; 3' long wood, cloth
  Parasol decorated with "83" and hand-painted peacock feather.
  98A-57
- Earrings/1945, 309; 1.5" acr. wood, plastic, paint
  Pair. Picture of woman on each. Sold to the Class of 1945 to aid Russian War Relief. See accompanying documentation.
  Belonged to Harriet L. Bodman 1945.
  98A-40
  paint badly chipped
- SC Pin/1922, 310; metal
  Belonged to Mary Ann Whitemore 1922.
  98A-55
- Class of 1926 Tote Bag/1971, 311; 10" x 11" cotton, felt
  Red tote bag with handle. "26" on side. Used at 45th reunion of Class of 1926.
  Belonged to Jane Pither Parker 1926.
- no artifact, 312
- Seahorse/1921, 313; 11" high ceramic
  Black with gold highlights. Mascot for Class of 1921.
- SC Mug/N.D., 314; 4" tall ceramic
  White mug. "Smith College Founded 1871" and Grecourt logo in blue.
- Class of 1912 Parasol/1967, 315; 3' long wood, cloth
  Black handle; purple cloth umbrella. Used at 55th reunion of Class of 1912. Theme: "The Great Society."
- Parasol/N.D., 316; 2.5' long wood, cloth
  Black handle with yellow cloth umbrella.
- Parasol/N.D., 317; 2' long wood, paper
  Black handle with heavy yellow paper umbrella.
- Class of 1932 Banner/N.D., 318; 5' x 9' cotton
  Batik purple banner with unicorn design by Deborah Davenport Brooks, daughter of Margery Witherell Davenport 1932.
- Dishtowel/N.D., 319; 16" x 25" cotton
  White towel with black silkscreen of crew boat. Reads "For the benefit of Smith Rowing". Coxswain saying, "Can't you wait till we get back!" Made by Woodchips Designers, Martha's Vineyard, MA.
  88A-146
- T-shirt/1989, 320; cotton
  Reads "No woman can call herself free who does not own and control her body. Margaret Sanger 1920" on front, and "Smith Women, National March for Women's Equality-Women's Lives. April 9, 1989".
  Margery Sly, College Archivist
  89A-69
- SC Fabric/N.D., 321; 22" x 17" cotton
  White with white SC logos silkscreened on cotton, dacron, or broadcloth. Sold for $6/yard, made by Natalie Galbreath Aust 1943, 8300 Bardmoor Blvd. Largo, FL 33543.
- SC Tablecloth/ N.D., 322; 4'4" x 5'10" linen
  SC buildings and scenes depicted in pink and cream.
  Emelie Sullivan Born 1956.
  87A-197
- SC Tablecloth/ N.D., 323; 4'4" x 5'10" linen
  SC buildings and scenes depicted in green and cream.
- Gillett House Sweatshirt/N.D., 324; cotton/ poly
  Turquoise with white lettering "Smith College / Gilletts Dance".
  Katie Schah 1998.
  97A-63
- Gillett House T-shirt/1993-94, 325; cotton
  White with pink and black writing: "Gillett House, 1993-94, Smith College" on front; "The Gillett, No Vacancy" on reverse.
- Morris House Rally Day Banner/1996, 326; 6'6" x 8'1" cloth, oil paint
  Rally Day banner in imitation of Michaelangelo's Sistene Chapel: Sophia Smith reaches out to touch Eve's finger. Reads "Celebrare Visum Sophiae-Domus Morris MCMXCVI". Won prize.
- Class of 1997 Rally Day Banner/1996, 327; 9' x 3'9" cotton, felt, paint
  Celebrating Sophia Smith Bicentennial. Reads "Celebrating Sophia's Vision and Ours! Education, Empowerment, Community, Growth, Friendship, Future, Class of 1997". Won prize.
  Karey Lance 1997.
- Emerson House Rally Day Banner/1996, 328; 8'8" x 3'10" cloth, paint
  Reads "Looking Ahead, Looking Back - 'If I put a little strength to oversome the difficulty the mountain would be removed, and I should have strength to make still further progress and I should more easily conquer difficulties' -Sophia Smith". Won prize.
  good. photo taken
- Centennial Tote Bag/1975, 329; 12" high canvas
  White bag with green print reading "Smith College Centennial 1875-1975".
- SC Staff Bicycle Plate/ N.D., 330; 3" acr. metal, paint
  Orange plate, #2.
- Meridians T-shirt/c. 1999, 331; Size S cotton
  T-shirt for Wesleyan-Smith journal Meridians: feminism, race, transnationalism.
  Given to Sherrill Redmon of SSC by Susan Van Dyne, Women's Studies Dept
- SC Spoon/N.D., 332; 6" silver
  Image of College Hall in bowl with initials "M.A." on face.
- Miniature Seelye Portraits/1904, 333 abc; 4" x 3" bronze
  Described under #57. Three. See accompanying documentation.
- T-shirt/1998, 334; Size L cotton
  Reads "Queer Activism/Queer Studies Symposium Nov. 6-8, 1998". White.
  Women's Studies Program
  98A-147
- SC Pin/1918, 335; gold
  Belonged to Clara Louise Curtiss 1918. Given by Sarah Strong Clapp 1950.
  98A-149
- T-shirt/1985, 336; Size M cotton/ poly
  Teal shirt reads "Jill Ker Conway / President / Smith College / Northampton, MA. A Decade of Down Under on Top 1975-1985".
  Given by Susan von Salis.
  98A-150
- SC Mug/1951, 337; china
  Name "Paula"-Paula Sharp - x51.
  Henry A. Rentschler.
  99A-18
- SC Spoon/N.D., 338; 6" silver
  "Smith College" on handle.
  Kate G. Stephenson 1933
  99A-24
- Class of 1892 Fan/N.D., 339; 9" x 12" cloth, wood, paint
  White fan with handpainted design of owl and shield. Sequins sewn on as part of design. Owl was Class of 1892 symbol. Used at a reunion.
- Basketball Uniform Jersey/1907, 340; 16" x 12" 16" x 14" collar wool, cotton, felt
  Blue with green numbers "1907". Green griffin on right sleeve. White collar with green trim. Collar attaches with hooks and buttons. Owner wrote inside collar the years she played.
  Belonged to Margaret D. Coe Blake 1907. From Helen (Mimi) Moog Cary 1941, whose mother, Helen Moodey 1907, was friends with Margaret.
  99A-69
- Class of 1924 Banner/N.D., 341; 54" x 36" felt
  Purple with white numbers "1924" and border, gold fringe. Used at reunions?
  Alumnae House-in 1924 class locker.
  99A- 73
- Class of 1924 Muff/N.D., 342; 7.5" x 11" felt
  Rectangular, purple with white "24".
  99A-73
- Reunion Skit Costume/1964, 343; Shirt: 24" x 22" Hat: 7.5" x 6.5" thin cloth, paper, canvas
  Prison uniform (shirt and hat) used in 40th Reunion skit of Class of 1924. Horiz. purple and white stripes, fits over head, card with "1924" on it in purple stapled to top. Hat small and round, canvas.
- Class of 1989 Toy Fish/1999, 344; foam-rubber
  Yellow and black squishy fish. Reads "Back to Paradise…Smith College Class of 1989 10th Year Reunion May 20-23 1999." Two fish.
  Class of 1989.
  99A-85
- Fish Magnet/ 1999, 345; magnet, metal
  Yellow and black fish. 10th year reunion of Class of 1989.
- Baseball Cap/N.D., 346; 7.25" wool
  Black with white SC logo.
- Keychain/1999, 347; 1" x 2" metal
  Class of 1989 10th Reunion keychain. Gold with black box, "Smith College Class of 1989 10th Year Reunion". See accompanying documentation.
- Class of 1989 T-shirt/N.D., 348; Size XL cotton
  White with caricatures of Nancy Reagan and Barbara Bush on front. Back reads: "There must be a better way to get a Smithie in the White House!"
- Class of 1989 T-shirt/N.D., 349; Size XL cotton
  White with yellow and black print: "Smith 1989".
- Head Residents T-shirt/1988-89, 350; Size XL cotton
  Pink. Front features arrow pointing to shoulder and words in black, "Place head here". Reverse reads "Head Residents Smith College 1988-89".
  Class of 1989
- Dragon Sculpture/N.D., 351; 10" x 8" paper, wire
  Green, with outstretched wings. Class of 1907 mascot?
- Baseball Cap/1999, 352; canvas
  "This is About Smith" on front. From 1999 Capital Campaign. Olive.
  Advancement Office via Judy Roberger.
- T-shirt/1999, 353; cloth
  "This is About Smith" on front and back. From 1999 Capital Campaign. Beige.
- Totebag/1999, 354; canvas
  "This is About Smith" on beige.
- Bag/1999, 355; coated paper
  "This is About Smith" on one side of white, shiny little bag.
- Pillowcase/ 1900, 356; cloth
  Image of a woman playing golf.
  Was in Room 33 of Hubbard House, September 1900.
  a bit soiled
- S Pin/c. 1950, 357; 0.25" x 1/8" metal
  Shape of an Old English "S." Awarded to outstanding athletes.
  Sarah S. Clapp 1950 Rec'd 5/13/2000.
  00A-39
- Class of 1909 Reunion Doll/1954, 358; 7.5" x 5.5" cloth, etc.
  From Class of 1909 55th Reunion.
  Donated at the May 2000 Reunion by Marjorie Jamison Douglas 1948 and Leigh Jamison Gifford, daughters of Marjorie Leigh Carr 1909.
  00A-54
- SC Pin/c. 1896, 359; 0.25" metal
  Gold diamond-shaped pin with "SC" in white enamel. See #411 for more information. See accompanying documentation.
  Belonged to Mary Louise Keller 1896. Given by Rosamond Horton Lownes 1954.
  00A-72
- T-shirt/1996, 360; Size L cotton
  Grey shirt with green and purple writing: "Smith College / Dedicated communIty Visionary tEam Resourceful Resourceful conStant talEnted" (capital letters spell "diverse").
  Bought by Margery Sly, College Archivist. Designed by Tracy Sutherland, Neilson Library Staff, 1996.
  96A-257
- Miniature Seelye Portrait/ 1910, 361; 3 1/8"x2.25" bronze
  Marcia Early Brocklebank 1959.
  00A-78
- Fan/c. 1900, 362; 13" paper, cord, bamboo
  White fan with various drawings on the back; front decorated with the names and seals of numerous colleges and universities. Created c. 1897-1900
  President's Office.
  00A-97
- Hard Hat/ c. 1985-1995, 363; plastic
  White with Smith stickers on front and sides and "Mary Dunn" on brim.
- Mwangi Center Banner/c. 1999, 364; 8' x 5'6" cotton/ poly, paint
  Reads "Our African Heritage-Remembering Not to Forget. Keynote Speaker Attallah Shabazz" in red and black paint.
  Abena Abrokwah 2001, Mwangi Center Coordinator 1998-99.
  00A-99
- Preludes Banner/1998, 365; 8'6" x 7'3" cotton/ poly, marker
  Each student attending Preludes drew an outline of her hand on the cloth, decorated it and then signed her name.
  Judith Hoffman 1999.
  00A-98
  discarded; photo taken
- Class of 1996 Rally Day Banner/1996, 366; 8'10" x 4' cotton, paint
  Reads, "Our future's so bright, Sophia would have to wear shades".
  Class of 1996
  00A-100
- Walking Cane and Seat/N.D., 367; 3' wood
  Small chair that collapses into a cane. Used for Class of 1919 Reunion. Green with "1919" on seat.
  Belonged to Bertha Tuttle Bowe 1919. From Cornelia T. Bowe 1947 and Kate Bowe Marmaras 1949.
  00A-101
- Ladies' Room Sign/N.D., 368; 8.5" x 10 0.75" paper, wood, poly, glass, metal, cloth
  Ladies' Room sign from Smith College Club. Made by Oliver Larkin.
  RADS
  00A- 122
- SC Medals/ N.D., 369 a&b; 2.5" across bronze
  Two. Described under #39.
  MRBR via B. Blumenthal.
  00A-123
- Spoon/1906, 370; 5" silver
  Spoon with "1906" on handle; donor believes it to be an SC spoon; not verified.
  Kate Stephenson 1933.
  00A-73
- SC Flag/N.D., 371; 6' x 7'8" nylon
  White background with gold-and-white SC diamond in middle.
  Pat Lisek, Building Services Coordinator.
  00A-136
- Player Piano Roll/c. 1902 or later, 372; 13.5" x 2" paper, wood
  Roll for song "The Smith College March and Two-Step" by E. M. Blake 1896. Manufactured by the Aeolian Co., 18 W. 23rd St. NYC. Roll # 8082. CA has sheet music for song in 52. Music SC Songs.
  From Sally Witt Duncan 1948.
  00A-139
  VERY brittle--should not be played
- Dewey House Banner/1991, 373; 4'4" x 6' cotton, marker
  Reads, "Dewey Women-Do We Ever!-Welcome". To welcome new students the last year that Dewey served as student housing. Signed by the upperclasswomen who lived there.
  Karen L. Alessi AC92, HR of Dewey 1991-92.
  00A-147
- Residence Life Quilt/1997-98, 374; 5'2" x 5'10" cotton, fabric paint
  Quilted banner with each square signed by a Head Resident (HR), House President (HP), or House Community Advisor (HCA).
  Residence Life.
  00A-156
- SC Hand-kerchief/N.D., 375; 8" x 8" cotton
  White with black silkscreen of Grecourt Gates and Ivy Day images.
- "Save Alumnae Gym" Button/ 1976, 376; 1.5" across metal
  Yellow background with black lettering. Used in campaign to stop the planned destruction of Alumnae Gym.
  Caroline Houser.
  01A-4
  a little rusty
- Ada Comstock Program Totebag/2000, 377; canvas
  Celebrating AC Program Silver Anniversary 1975-2000.
  AC Program.
  01A-64
- New Yorker Cartoon Plate/N.D., 378; 5.25" across ceramic
  Black and white featuring New Yorker cartoon with two women at table saying "Isn't it wonderful to feel that once a Smith girl, always a Smith girl?"
  From Monmouth County Smith Club.
- Class of 1953 Reunion Plate/ 1973, 379; 10" across ceramic
  White plate, do-it-yourself decorations. Reads, "Born Free / A Gathering of Our 'Pride' / 20th Reunion". Plate by Texas-ware.
- Loving Cup Trophy/1946, 380; stainless steel
  Skidelsky Cup reading, "For the Most Meritorious Exhibit / Awarded to Smith College 1939-1946". For Chrysanthemum Show?
  Botanical Gardens via Maryjane Beach.
  01A-67
- Loving Cup Trophy/1951, 381; silver
  Reads, "George J. Ball for the Meritorious Exhibit Awarded to Smith College 1951".
- Trophy Bowl/1953, 382; silver
  Holyoke Transcript Telegram Trophy. Presented to Holyoke-Northampton Florists and Gardeners Club for Best Cascade Chrysanthemum. SC won in 1953, 1954, 1957.
- Trophy Bowl/1950, 383; silver
  "Presented to the Holyoke-Northampton Gardeners Club by the Holyoke Transcript-Telegram for the Best Cascade Chrysanthemum". Awarded to SC 1948-50.
- Gorokhoff Medal Mold/N.D., 384; 6.5" across plaster
  Plaster mold for medal of Ivan Gorokhoff.
  Gregor Trinkhaus-Randall.
  01A-70
- Handkerchief/ c. 1919, 385; 14" x 14" linen
  White with red silkscreen.
  Belonged to Clara Helen Gibson 1919.
- Class of 1990 Reunion Box/2000, 386; 1.5" across tin or alum.
  Round box given out for Class of 1990 10th Reunion. Red with "'90 Smith" on lid. Originally held mints.
- Basketball Centennial Paperweight/ 1991, 387; 2" x 3"x 1" marble, metal
  Reads, "Basketball Centennial 1891-1991" and "Women's Centennial Luncheon 12-19-91".
  From Office of the President, MMD.
  95A-111
- SCSW Paperweight/ c. 1985-95, 388; 2 0.75" x 2 0.75" x 1" clear resin
  Clear paperweight; reads, "1918 Fellowship of Special Giving" and "SCSW".
- Capital Campaign Paperweight/ c. 1985-95, 389; 3 0.75" x 2 0.75" x 1" clear resin
  Clear paperweight; reads "The Campaign for Smith".
- SC Basketball Centennial Paperweight/ 1992, 390; 3" x 3" x 1" wood
  Reads, "Women's Basketball Centennial / Smith College 1892-1992" and "100".
- Comstock House Baseball Cap/c. 1985-95, 391; canvas
  Reads, "Comstock / Smith College". White cap with red and black lettering.
- Lawrence House T-shirt/N.D., 392; Size XL cotton
  White t-shirt with black-and-red image of a television with TV logos on front. "Lawrence House: The Truth is in Here" on reverse. Given to President MMD upon leaving SC in 1995.
- Park House T-shirt/1993-94, 393; Size XL cotton
  Purple with orange lettering. Reads, "bark house 1993-1994" on front with little cartoon, and "my dog likes you" on reverse. Given to President MMD upon leaving SC in 1995.
- Albright House T-shirt/1995, 394; Size XL cotton
  White with large red "A" on front and "Albright House Smith College 1994-95" on reverse. Long-sleeved. With student signatures and messages in black ink. Given to President MMD upon leaving SC in 1995.
- Laura Scales House T-shirt/1994-95, 395; Size L cotton
  White shirt with black print. "Laura Scales House Smith College 1994-1995" on front. Cartoon on back, and words, "The House of Swingin' Singles". Given to President MMD upon leaving SC in 1995.
- Bridge Program T-shirt/1994, 396; XXL cotton
  Yellow with grey, black, and red print. Bridge logo and year on front. Given to President MMD upon leaving SC in 1995.
- Smithstock T-shirt/1994, 397; XL cotton
  White with multicolored design of bird on woman symbol and words "1994 Smithstock" and "One More Night of Peace and Music". Given to President MMD upon leaving SC in 1995.
- SC T-shirt/N.D., 398; Size XL cotton
  Words tracing the process between "Application" and "Reunion" on front; "Just Do It Smith College" on reverse. Given to President MMD upon leaving SC in 1995.
- Class of 1989 Reunion T-shirt/1994, 399; Size XL cotton
  White with yellow design and black lettering. "'89 Shines! Smith College" on front and "5th Reunion / Class of 1989 / May 26th-29th, 1994 / Smith College / Northampton, Massachusetts". Given to President MMD upon leaving SC in 1995.
- Otelia Cromwell Day T-shirt/1989, 400; Size XL cotton/ poly
  Image of Otelia Cromwell on front and "Otelia Cromwell Day: Celebrating Diversity at Smith November 9, 1989".
  a bit worn
- Museum of Art T-shirt/N.D., 401; Size XXL cotton
  Image of headless, naked, female statue on front, "Smith College Museum of Art: Ahead of the Rest" on reverse. Cream shirt with black and red print.
- Five Colleges T-shirt/N.D., 402; Size XL cotton
  Teal t-shirt with navy and white print. "Five Colleges" on front and "Cooperation is an unnatural act" on reverse.
- SC Campus School Tote Bag/N.D., 403; 16" x 13" canvas
  Red tote bag with stick figures and lettering in tan. Reads, "Smith College Campus School". Tan handles.
- SC Seal/N.D., 404; 11" x 10" metal, wood
  Seal on black wood, shape of shield.
- Botanic Garden Sign/c. 1995, 405; 4.5" x 6" metal, plastic
  Silvery surface, black inset lettering. Reads, "The Mary Maples Dunn Garden, The Botanic Garden of Smith College".
- Paperweight/ 1898?, 406; 4" x 2.5" glass, paper, felt
  Rectangular; depicts gates of SC before Grecourt Gates installed. Mailman in left corner of picture. See accompanying documentation.
  Found in 43F in box labelled "Smith College Mementos" January 2002. Given by Annette O'Leary 1935.
  photo is yellowing, felt backing peeling off
- Adjustable Candle Holder/N.D., 407; circ. base 7" across; shaft 2" across; 9" high wrought iron
  Large, black taper holder with elaborate tripod base, spiral/spring-shaped shaft, and handle. Mechanism allows for candle to be wound upward as wax melts.
  Found in 43F in box labeled "Smith College Mementos" January 2002.
  fine; winding mechanism still works
- Picture Frame/N.D., 408; sides are 9" & 7"; frame 5" x 7" wood, glass?, twine
  Rectangular, brown, wooden picture frame with white (glass?) baubles at corners. Sides extend past corners. See accompanying documentation.
  Found in 43F in box labeled "Smith College Mementos" January 2002. Belonged to Henry P. Cook.
  No picture; not clear if picture was lost or intentionally not given with frame.
- Barbells/N.D., 409; 10" x 3" ea. wood
  Light dumbbells used in early gym exercises. One bears name "Hallie Williams." See accompanying documentation.
  fine; wood warping a bit
- Stationery Set/N.D., 410; stamper: 4" x 2.25" holder: 4" x 2 0.75" brass
  Letter holder and stamper/sealer (?) with SC seal in shield.
  Found in 43F in box labelled "Smith College Mementos" January 2002.
- SC Pin/N.D., 411; 3/4" gold
  Gold diamond-shaped pin with "SC" in white enamel. Also called "Senior pins:" see accompanying documentation for SC/Senior Pins. All pins have owners' name or initials engraved on the back.
  Belonged to Mary Stewart Anthony 1883.
- SC Pin/N.D., 412; 3/4" gold
  See Item # 411.
  Belonged to Nina Browne 1882.
- SC Pin/1895, 413; 3/4" gold
  Belonged to Mabel H. Cummings 1895.
- SC Pin/1900, 414; 3/4" gold
  Belonged to Julia B. Paton 1900.
- SC Pin/1901, 415; 3/4" gold
  Belonged to Dora L. Clifford 1901.
- SC Pin/1904, 416; 3/4" gold
  Belonged to Miriam A. Choate 1904.
- SC Pin/N.D., 417; 3/4" gold
  See Item # 411. See accompanying documentation.
  Belonged to Kate (Morris) Cone 1879.
- SC Pin/1896, 418; 3/4" gold
  Belonged to Miriam W. Webb 1896.
- SC Pin/1901, 419; 3/4" gold
  Belonged to Anna L. Johson 1901.
- SC Pin/1904, 420; 3/4" gold
  Belonged to Marion Dana 1904.
- SC Pin/1904, 421; 3/4" gold
  Belonged to Anna Russ 1904.
- SC Pin/1893, 422; 3/4" gold
  Belonged to E.P.C. 1893.
- SC Pin/1904, 423; 3/4" gold
  Belonged to Louise E. Fuller 1904.
- SC Pin/1907, 424; 3/4" gold
  Belonged to Catharine D. Allison 1907.
- SC Pin/1909, 425; 3/4" gold
  Belonged to Elizabeth S. Allison 1909.
- SC Pin/1912, 426; 3/4" gold
  Belonged to Elsie (Becker) O'Quist 1912.
- SC Pin/1915, 427; 3/4" gold
  Belonged to Charlotte C. Pearce 1915.
- SC Pin/1916, 428; 3/4" gold
  Belonged to Lucile J. Driscoll 1916.
- SC Pin/1927, 429; 3/4" gold
  Belonged to Sara Gribbon 1927.
- SC Pin/1931, 430; 3/4" gold
  Belonged to Louise (Wolff) Kahn 1931.
- SC Pin/1896, 431; 3/4" gold
  Belonged to Martha Davis Hale 1896. Sent by Polly Harts Kellogg 1922 in May 1977.
- SC Pin/1907, 432; 3/4" gold
  Belonged to Clara (Senior) Iglauer 1907. Sent by dau. Laura I. Youngs, rec'd 6/23/80.
- Class Pin/1896, 433; 3/4" enamel on gold
  White "S" curling through light purple "96".
  Belonged to Martha Davis Hale 1896. Sent by Polly Harts Kellogg 1922.
  enamel chipped
- Class Pin/1896, 434; 3/4" enamel on gold
  White "S" curling through dark purple "96".
- Class Pin/1897, 435; 3/4" x 1/4" enamel on gold
  White enamel on gold shield shape, gold filigree and lettering: "S" and "97."
  Belonged to Harriet Hallock 1897.
- Class Pin/1897, 436; 3/4" x 1/4" enamel on gold
- Class Pin/1899, 437; 3/4" enamel on gold
  Green enamel circle with "99" in gold. Gold heraldic branches circling up to "S" in white enamel.
  Belonged to Miriam F. Choate 1899.
- Class Pin/1901, 438; 1/2" enamel on gold
  Gold diamond with angular "SC" in black. White enamel banner across bottom with "1901" in gold.
  Belonged to Madelaine (?) Rogers 1901.
- Class Pin/1901, 439; 1/2" enamel on gold
- Class Pin/1901, 440; 1/2" enamel on gold
  Belonged to Jane L. Emerson 1901.
- Class Pin/1902, 441; 1/2" enamel on gold
  Angular gold "S" forming a diamond shape; red bar in center with "1902" in gold.
  Belonged to F.W.V.
  dull
- Class Pin/1903, 442; 1/2" enamel on gold
  Gold square at diamond angle, fleurs-de-lis at corners. "S" and "1903" in gold on green enamel diamond in center.
  Belonged to Edith Hill 1903.
- Class Pin/1903, 443; 1/2" enamel on gold
  Belonged toHelen E. Allen 1903.
- Class Pin/1904, 444; 1/2" across enamel on gold
  Gold circle with "S" and "1904" in relief, surrounded by pearlescent purple enamel.
  Belonged to Annetta Clark 1904.
- Class Pin/1904, 445; 1/2" across enamel on gold
- Class Pin/1904, 446; 1/2" across enamel on gold
- Class Pin/1904, 447; 1/2" across enamel on gold
- Class Pin/1905, 448; 1/2" gold
  Angular "S" and "C" forming a near-square, "1905" in center in black.
- Class Pin/1906, 449; 1/2" enamel on gold
  Gold nauga-snake curled around red enamel bar with "06" in gold.
  Belonged to M. Gail Tritch 1906
- Class Pin/1906, 450; 1/2" enamel on gold
  Gold shield divided into three sections: top left has "SC" and "1906" in red on gold. Top right has a dragon in red between two white columns, on gold. Bottom has raised image of a book, rendered in white with gold lettering, on red.
  Belonged to M. Gail Tritch.
- Class Pin/1906, 451; 1/2" enamel on gold
  See Item #450.
  Belonged to Susan (Tanner) Larkin 1906. Sent by dau. Eleanor L. Beardsley in 5/1979.
- Class Pin/1907, 452; 1/2" enamel on gold
  SC in gold wreathed with "07" in green.
  Belonged to Catherine Allison 1907.
- Class Pin/1907, 453; 1/2" enamel on gold
  Belonged to Clara (Senior) Iglauer 1907. Sent by dau. Laura I. Youngs, 6/23/1980.
- Class Pin/1908, 454; 1/2" gold
  Square "SC" with "08" raised in center.